A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Civic Engagement and Government Program, Office Files of Amy Brown FA1846
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant files, 2008-2016; 2; 6.08 Cubic Feet 16 document boxes: 16 letter size boxes
  - National League of Cities (NLCI) - Local Interventions for Financial Empowerment through Utility Payments (LIFT-UP) (Grant No. 0150-0614-0), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 150)
    Request No. 124146
  - National Federation of Community Development Credit Unions (NFCDCU) (Grant No. 0150-0770-0), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 151)
    Request No. 125149
  - National People's Action (NPA) - Consumer Lending Coalition, 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 152)
    Request No. 123490
  - New Economy Project - Community Financial Justice Initiative (Grant No. 0150-0489-0), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 153)
    Request No. 123473
  - Self-Help Ventures Fund (Grant No. 0150-0525-0), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 154)
    Request No. 123481
  - Washington University - Refund to Savings (Grant No. 0140-0622-0), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 155)
    Request No. 125427
  - Center for Community Change (CCC) - Young Invincibles (YI) (Grant No. 0150-0844-0), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 156)
    Request No. 125274
  - Filene Research Institute - Accessible Financial Services Incubator (Grant No. 0130-1099-0), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 157)
    Request No. 123484